CURRICULUM VITAE.

CHRISTOPHER OYUGA OGWENO.

P. O BOX 55742-00200 NAIROBI. lchristopheroyuga@gmail.com +254790807686.

Kenyan. | single. | 25 years old.

LANGUAGE. | English, Kiswahili. | Fluent.

WEBSITE DESIGNER & I.T SPECIALIST.



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:

I'm a highly motivated Information Technology (I.T) professional with extensive experience in providing Technical Assistance, installation and troubleshooting for a wide range of software and hardware and advanced knowledge of computer information Technology. Have Diploma in Information Communication Technology with one years working experience.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Ass office Admin (receptionist.). | MADISON GROUP ASSURANCE- MOMBASA. | 12TH October 2024- NOW.

Network Maintenance. | EMBA CONNECT, Embakasi-Nairobi. | 10th May 2024- 20th October 2024.

- Performed troubleshooting and fix problem on network issues.
- Optimizing network performance, regular backing up data.
- Enforcing network security measures.

COMPETENCES:

- Data management.
- Data analysis.
- Coding.
- Decision making.
- Team management.
- Data security.

- Communication skills.
- MS Word, excel, Access, Spreadsheet.
- Customer services.
- Computer languages. (html, C. s. s, java, c++.)

EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATION:

Diploma (I.C.T) | N.Y. S Engineering Institute. | Nairobi.

12TH May 2021- 10TH April 2024

- Module 1. PASS.
 - i. Computer mathematics
 - ii. ICT Ethics.
 - iii. C programming.
 - iv. Pascal.
- Module II. CREDIT.
 - i. System Analysis and Design.
 - ii. Database management.
 - iii. Object oriented programming.
- Module III. DISTINCTION.
 - i. Internet Base programming.
 - ii. Data communication and Networking.
 - iii. Principle and practice of management

ATARCHMENT:

KenGen | KIPEVU Unit. | Mombasa.

10TH May-30TH Nov 2023.

10TH May-30TH Nov 2023.

Skills Attained.

- i. Networking.
- ii. Computer security.
- iii. System update and management.

Amref Health Africa Training.

- i. Community Health.
- ii. First Aid.
- iii. HIV measure and control.

Paramilitary Training. | National Youth Service. | Gilgil.

27TH June 2019 - 20TH DEC 2019.

- i. Paramilitary training.
- ii. Discipline and drills. NYS Act.
- iii. First Aid.

Certificate (computer packages). | Tebotech Training Institute. | Mombasa.

4TH FEB 2018 - 24TH Nov 2018.

12 packages. (MS word. Excel. Access.)

Certificate (KCSE). | Obanga Mixed Sec. School.

12TH Jan 2014 - 20TH Nov 2017.

C plain -42 points.

STRENGTH:

- Great communication skills: the skill enables me to interact with employer, fellow workers and also on handling clients.
- Excellent Problem- solving skills: the potential to interact with problems, determinations towards the challenge's solution leads excellency.
- Self-Discipline: always smart on every work am doing, transparency and honesty.
- Passion for Technology: always determine to learn, peruse and go deep in the field of Technology.

PROFESIONAL HIGHLIGHTS:

- · Critical thinking.
- Teamwork and collaboration.

REFEREE:

Madam Winnie Ongolo. | ICT SUPERVISOR. | KenGen.

0724485889.

Jimmy Mbugu. | C.E. O EMBACONNECT. | Nairobi.

0706176053.

Carolita Ngingi. | H.O. D NYS Engineering Institute. | Nairobi.

0721467829.